[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former British colony joined the European Union in 2004?", "correct_answer": "Malta", "incorrect_answers": ["Gibraltar", "Ireland", "Syria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This flower opens up in sunny weather. When rain is expected, it closes tightly.", "correct_answer": "Scarlet Pimpernel", "incorrect_answers": ["Primrose", "Nasturtium", "Daisy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This dog breed was developed as a gun dog in Canada?", "correct_answer": "Labrador Retriever", "incorrect_answers": ["Mountain Cur", "Pharaoh Hound", "Lakeland Terrier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 2007 Angelina Jolie received this award from the International Rescue Committee.", "correct_answer": "Freedom Award", "incorrect_answers": ["Peace Award", "Award for Raising Awareness", "White Dove Award"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many fingers did the Tyrannosaurus rex have on its forelimbs?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "3", "5"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, The African Queen, Charlie and Rose saw what animals, causing Charlie to warn Rose that they are more dangerous than they look?", "correct_answer": "A group of hippos", "incorrect_answers": ["A flock of flamingos", "A herd of elephants", "A band of chimpanzees"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Greek mythological hero eloped with King Menelaus wife, Helen, thus prompting the Trojan War?", "correct_answer": "Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["Priam", "Hector", "Achilles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diet of most parrots consists of this type of food.", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Buds", "Fruit", "Seeds"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pigeon and dove fossils are regularly found giving us a lot of information on pigeon evolution?", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movie was the line, Ill be back delivered?", "correct_answer": "The Terminator", "incorrect_answers": ["The Matrix Reloaded", "Back to the Future", "The Matrix"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Of how many pieces does the traditional Sino-European domino set consist?", "correct_answer": "28", "incorrect_answers": ["16", "32", "30"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of duct is the Whartons duct found in the human body?", "correct_answer": "Salivary duct", "incorrect_answers": ["Tear duct", "Sweat duct", "Bile duct"]}]